{
    "subject": "resource/Hot_Wacks",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Hot Wacks is a Canadian book that has been in circulation for over 25 years, featuring reviews of bootleg music releases. Reviews include information such as source, quality, track listing and packaging. It is commonly referred to as the 'Bootleg Bible' by bootleg collectors. Hot Wacks was the work of Kurt Glemser.",
    "human_readable": "The comment about Hot Wacks is that it's a Canadian book that has been in circulation for over 25 years, featuring reviews of bootleg music releases, including information such as source, quality, track listing and packaging, which is commonly referred to as the 'Bootleg Bible' by bootleg collectors, and was written by Kurt Glemser.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8744036555290222,
            "question": "What information about bootleg music releases does 'Hot Wacks' provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8566821217536926,
            "question": "What kind of details about bootlegs are included in 'Hot Wacks'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8446763753890991,
            "question": "Is 'Hot Wacks' a recognized resource for bootleg music collectors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8444580435752869,
            "question": "What nickname is given to 'Hot Wacks' by bootleg collectors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8164482116699219,
            "question": "What type of music releases are reviewed in 'Hot Wacks'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8097366094589233,
            "question": "Besides track listings, what other information does 'Hot Wacks' offer about bootlegs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7905828952789307,
            "question": "How long has 'Hot Wacks' been in circulation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7667110562324524,
            "question": "Who wrote the book 'Hot Wacks'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6995114088058472,
            "question": "What is the main focus of the book 'Hot Wacks'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5837230682373047,
            "question": "What is the nationality of the book 'Hot Wacks'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about Hot Wacks is that it's a Canadian book that has been in circulation for over 25 years, featuring reviews of bootleg music releases, including information such as source, quality, track listing and packaging, which is commonly referred to as the 'Bootleg Bible' by bootleg collectors, and was written by Kurt Glemser.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2192_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main focus of the book 'Hot Wacks'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2192_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who wrote the book 'Hot Wacks'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2192_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How long has 'Hot Wacks' been in circulation?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2192_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2192_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2192_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2192_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2192_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2192_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2192_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2192_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2192_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2192_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2192_46.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents indeed mention that Hot Wacks is a book about bootlegs with lists of bootlegs available at the time, commonly referred to as the 'Bootleg Bible' by bootleg collectors. Additionally, it mentions that Kurt Glemser was the creator of Hot Wacks."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation of the query and documents:\n\n- The information about Hot Wacks includes:\n  - It is a Canadian book that has been in circulation for over 25 years.\n  - It features reviews of bootleg music releases, including source, quality, track listing, and packaging.\n  - It is commonly referred to as the 'Bootleg Bible' by bootleg collectors.\n  - The author was Kurt Glemser.\n\nAll these details align with the statement provided in the query. Therefore, the response is \"yes.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}